https://www.sloroasted.com/index.php?main_page=privacy

Limited Roast & Crown Jewel Coffees...
Same Day Shipping on Orders Received by 1:00pm, Monday - FridayFree Shipping on Orders of $50 or more!
Don't Just Drink Coffee, Enjoy It!
Discover
Coffee Rating Terminology - What Does it Mean?
Shop
Coffee by the K-CupCoffee by the Portion PackCoffee by the Filter PouchCoffee by the PoundCoffee by the BagTea by the BoxCoffee FiltersCoffee Brewing GearCoffee ArtHoliday GiftsSLO Roasted Logo ItemsCoffee Infused EdiblesAll Products ...
Home
Privacy Notice
Privacy Notice
Effective: 01/01/2014
Our Commitment To Privacy
Your privacy is important to us. We consider the information you choose to share with us personal and confidential. We will not sell any of your information, period! To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices. To make this notice easy to find, we provide a link to this document within the footer of our website.
The Information We Collect:
This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the our website. On some pages, you can order products, make requests, and register to receive materials. The types of personal information collected at these pages are:
Name
Address
Email address
Phone number
Credit/Debit Card Information
Etc.
On some pages, you can submit information about other people. For example, if you order a gift online and want it sent directly to the recipient, you will need to submit the recipient's address. In this circumstance, the types of personal information collected are:
Name
Address
Phone Number
Etc.
The Way We Use Information:
We use the information you provide about yourself when placing an order only to complete that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order.
We use the information you provide about someone else when placing an order only to ship the product and to confirm delivery. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order.
We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties.
We use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our website for you, our customers.
Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses.
Our Commitment To Data Security
To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.
Our Commitment To Children's Privacy:
Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13.
How You Can Access Or Correct Your Information
You can access all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain by logging in to our site and selecting the "My Account" link. We use this procedure to better safeguard your information.
To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.
Why We use Cookies
Our sites use cookies to keep track of your shopping cart contents and to deliver content specific information. Most internet browsers allow you to control the kind of cookies you automatically accept or whether you accept cookies at all. Please refer to your Internet browser's instructions for instructions on enabling cookies.
How To Contact Us
Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please use our Contact Us form.
Monday - Friday:
6:00am to 5:00pm PST
Closed Dec 25th & Jan 1st
Closed at 12pm on Dec 24th & Dec 31st
Our Mission: To Bring value to our customers beyond their expectations.
Copyright © 2020 SLO Roasted Coffee:: Site Developed byWrightWorkx
